let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "______ is not a Popup box in JavaScript",
        answer:"D. Error",
        options: [
            "A. Confirm",
            "B. Prompt",
            "C. Alert",
            "D. Error"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Where is the map definition file generally stored?",
        answer:"B. CGI-BIN",
        options: [
            "A. Recycle bin",
            "B. CGI-BIN",
            "C. Bin",
            "D. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which one of the following is an example of an ‘internet search engine?",
        answer:"B. Google",
        options: [
            "A. LINUX",
            "B. Google",
            "C. MS Word",
            "D. Windows"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "At which port number, Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) operates",
        answer:"D. 161",
        options: [
            "A. 160",
            "B. 163",
            "C. 164",
            "D. 161"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which of the following is not an HTML tag?",
        answer:"D. < list >",
        options: [
            "A. < select >",
            "B. < input >",
            "C. < textarea >",
            "D. < list >"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which among these is not a Web browser?",
        answer:"A. www",
        options: [
            "A. www",
            "B. Chrome",
            "C. Opera",
            "D. NetSurf"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "World Wide Web was invented by",
        answer:"B. Tim Berners-Lee",
        options: [
            "A. Ted Nelson",
            "B. Tim Berners-Lee",
            "C. Linus Torvalds",
            "D. Robert E. Kahn"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What does HTML stand for?",
        answer:"A. Hyper Text Markup Language",
        options: [
            "A. Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "B. High Text Markup Language",
            "C. Hyper Tabular Markup Language",
            "D. None of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which of the following statements is true regarding HTTP?",
        answer:"B. It does not maintain any connection information on previous transactions",
        options: [
            "A. Web browsers use only HTTP as a communication protocol with servers",
            "B. It does not maintain any connection information on previous transactions",
            "C. It is designed to route information based on content",
            "D. It refers to resources using their Universal Resource Identifier (URI)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which one among these is used with tag as an attribute to specify alternate text for an image, if the image is not displayed for some reason?",
        answer:"A. Alt",
        options: [
            "A. Alt",
            "B. Alternate",
            "C. Duplicate",
            "D. Auxiliary"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Which among the following options is correct regarding HTML?",
        answer:"D. Used to structure web documents",
        options: [
            "A. Modelling Language",
            "B. DTP language",
            "C. Partial programming language",
            "D. Used to structure web documents"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "HTTPs stands for",
        answer:"A. Hyper Text Transfer Protocol Secure",
        options: [
            "A. Hyper Text Transfer Protocol Secure",
            "B. High Text Transfer Protocol Secure",
            "C. Hyper Transfer Protocol Secure",
            "D. Hyper Transfer Protocol Standard"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "XML stands for",
        answer:"B. Extensible Markup Language",
        options: [
            "A. Extensible Mask Language",
            "B. Extensible Markup Language",
            "C. Extended Markup Language",
            "D. Extension Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Which of the following is NOT true regarding JavaScript?",
        answer:"B. JavaScript is event driven",
        options: [
            "A. JavaScript is a loosely typed language",
            "B. JavaScript is event driven",
            "C. JavaScript is not an object-based language",
            "D. JavaScript can not run in standalone mode"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "What are Empty elements and is it valid?",
        answer:"B. Empty elements are element with no data",
        options: [
            "A. No, there are no such terms as Empty Elements",
            "B. Empty elements are element with no data",
            "C. No, it is not valid to use Empty Element",
            "D. None of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "Which method of the Component class is used to set the position and size of a component in JSP?",
        answer:"B. setBounds()",
        options: [
            "A. setSize()",
            "B. setBounds()",
            "C. setPosition()",
            "D. setPositionSize()"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "In JSP, a Canvas object provides access to a Graphics object via one of its method called",
        answer:"C. paint()",
        options: [
            "A. getCanvas()",
            "B. getGraphics()",
            "C. paint()",
            "D. getPaint()"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "How can you open a link in a new browser window?",
        answer:"B. < a href = “url” target= “_blank” >",
        options: [
            "A. < a href = “url” target = “new” >",
            "B. < a href = “url” target= “_blank” >",
            "C. < a href = “url”.new >",
            "D. < a href = “url” target =”open” >"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "The tag used to create a hypertext relationship between current document and another URL is",
        answer:"C. < LINK >",
        options: [
            "A. < ISINDEX >",
            "B. < A >",
            "C. < LINK >",
            "D. None of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "Which tag creates a number/order list?",
        answer:"B. < OL >",
        options: [
            "A. < UL >",
            "B. < OL >",
            "C. < OT >",
            "D. None of these"
        ]
    }, 
]